[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Mail delivery.
Came three times, but nobody was home.
Oh, you're home.
Lane 75, Number Two.
I came three times, and nobody was home.
Had to catch you right as my shift began.
I haven't seen you around before.
Did you just move in?
Anything fragile in here?
Open it and check.
Once you sign, we take no responsibility.
What a mute.
Your rear brake pads are almost worn out.
Remember to change them.
Also, if you were quicker and came early,
you wouldn't have wasted three trips.
Such a mute,
but he sure has a nasty mouth.
Everyone, fall in and face me.
Watch your step getting off.
Hurry up.
Keep up.
Hurry up in the back.
Gather at the front after getting off.
Right, dress!
Eyes front!
At ease!
Attention!
Right, face!
Forward, march!
The new place is quite nice.
There are no issues.
You don't need to worry.
The things sent from home,
I received them this morning.
I'll be very busy for a while.
Please don't tell anyone.
If anyone asks,
just say I went traveling.
I went over everything from the start.
Meeting Jiang Zaizhen in Hong Kong, China,
to her landing overseas,
then entering the safe house,
and finally boarding the plane directly.
All along the way,
someone was tipping off Taiwan, China.
This person
is among us.
Are you sure?
Maybe there's more than one.
Maybe there will be more.
Jiang Zaizhen
saw a top-secret file in Taipei herself.
She's very certain
that the enemy has breached our defenses.
If we don't plug the hole,
the leaks will keep coming.
We can talk about the future tomorrow.
Let's talk about yesterday first.
Who do you think it is?
It's hard to say.
Is it hard to say,
or you just can't say?
Does it look like him?
What does shaking your head mean?
No,
I just can't be sure.
Take the leaked intel Jiang Zaizhen cited
and compile it for me.
I'll arrange for someone
to start investigating from this point.
Did she say anything else?
Taiwan, China will send new people soon.
The scale is unprecedented.
It includes their official agents,
as well as corrupted youths from our side.
Lee Teng-hui aims to "visit the US."
If this happens,
it will be the fuse.
People on both sides will prepare for it.
All intelligence channels will activate.
The missiles are a highly coveted prize.
You need to lock them down tight for me.
When the time comes,
Mawei Naval Port, the military compound,
Institutes 761, 762, and 766.
It's a massive game of chess.
All the pieces will start moving.
How big will our moves be?
If Taiwan, China makes a knight move,
I'll counter with a central cannon
and put them in check.
Director.
The Jiang Zaizhen case happened suddenly.
None of us can guarantee
if there are other moles among us.
The stakes are high.
Cross-strait military intel's success
might depend on this one move.
We can't afford any mistakes.
Openly create a diversion.
Interrogate everyone,
starting with myself.
Please detain me publicly,
while I secretly head to Germany
to execute our real plan.
Yes, sir.
Which way is the Aviation Power booth?
It's the one at this exhibition
featuring that outstanding project.
That booth should be in Zone A.
It's the largest booth on the corner.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I found out.
It's right over there.
Follow me.
Sorry.
It's okay.
How do we make the missile's tail ignite
to fly faster, higher, and farther?
Master foreign skills to counter them.
The wider the gap, the more we must learn.
Fighting for titles at home is useless.
If you don't open your eyes to the world,
it's a dead end.
Practice is more important than theory.
Researchers can't work in a vacuum.
We need to get out and see the world.
You have a lot of eggs,
but you lack the
power and speed to throw them out.
Once others get ahead of you,
no matter how many eggs you have,
they'll all break in the nest.
We've been studying arm strength,
studying carts full of eggs,
to throw them faster and more accurately.
We were wrong.
Think about it.
Since we can't increase the cart's speed,
why don't we start with the fuel?
Use the speed of the fuel
to make up for the speed of the cart.
That's it for work today.
Let's drink tonight.
We won't leave until we're drunk.
Alright!
Mainlanders...
are just so much trouble.
Hosting is definitely no problem.
We Ronghai people love making friends.
Wining and dining are small matters.
I'm doing business here,
I'm not a professional tour guide, right?
Boss Wen.
I'll talk to you later.
Leader Cao, this way!
Long time no see! Long time no see!
Let me introduce him to everyone.
Boss Wen Zongshu.
A friend of Director Lei,
and also our fellow Ronghai native.
He does massive business in Europe.
And he's very hospitable.
The hotel and cars for our trip this time
were all arranged by Boss Wen for us.
Hello, hello, hello.
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
I worried you wouldn't beat the jet lag.
Initially, as soon as you landed, I wanted
to invite you to dinner.
Right next door,
are some great specialty restaurants.
Sound good?
This way.
Let's go, let's go.
Where else do you want to go this time?
This time we're mainly visiting
Hamburg, Berlin, and Munich.
Just these three places.
Europe isn't actually that big.
Since you're already here,
why not visit other countries?
Time is too tight this time.
Baby!
What are you doing?!
What do you want?
Take your hands off!
Foreigners are all like that.
They're a bit more open.
Yes, very open.
And they're still not used to it.
Hello.
Let's just ignore them.
Let's go our own way.
Hey friend.
Hello, friend.
Hello.
What's going on here? What's going on?
Stop!
What's wrong?
Stop right there!
Don't run!
Who is it?
Mr. Cao, here are your painkillers.
I didn't buy any painkillers.
Boss Wen sent you to deliver them, right?
Come in, have a seat.
My surname is Zhu.
My given name is Yingjia.
I've lived in Taiwan, China a long time.
Serving in the ROC Ministry of Defense
as a Military Intelligence Bureau Colonel.
This is not Minzhong.
Nor is it Taipei.
No one can hear us talking.
It's very safe.
I'd like ten minutes of your time
for a heart-to-heart talk
and to make a friend.
Lao Jia! Lao Jia!
Lao Jia!
Call the police.
Maricotre Hotel.
Someone's trying to rape an underage girl.
We need you here immediately.
Your friend was a bit too impatient.
This girl just turned fourteen yesterday.
In Germany,
having sex with a minor is illegal.
Liaoping, I'm innocent!
Beiyuan Longbei.
Dragon-Phoenix tea cakes.
I couldn't get Song Dynasty tributes.
I only have this modest gift,
to show my sincerity.
I'm an unrefined man.
I don't know tea, I just drink it blindly.
Unlike you, who has the taste to be picky.
I had someone get this tea from Ronghai.
The leaves are plump.
The color is dark and glossy.
Once brewed, the aroma is lasting.
Try it while it's hot.
You even know what kind of tea I like.
Making friends is like courting a girl.
If I ask her out to dinner,
I'd want to know her favorite food.
But I prefer coffee.
Hence the face-to-face communication.
The more we talk,
the more we understand each other.
Out of all the experts in the delegation,
that I'd be the one to turn traitor?
That's impossible.
You are exceptionally good at your work.
Truly brilliant.
At the 761 Institute,
every major technological breakthrough
comes from your department.
But you have a unique personality.
You'd spend three months' pay on a watch.
You chose not to have kids.
You live a carefree life.
You never kiss up to anyone.
Despite your work, they won't value you.
You have complaints and grievances.
Unfortunately,
they were heard by the higher-ups.
Having you lead this delegation to Europe
was an excuse to promote someone else.
Research units only value one achievement:
academic achievement.
Promotion or not doesn't matter to me.
It's just a matter of face.
However,
your relatives haven't repaid their loans,
and your ancestral home needs renovation.
Financial holes must be filled eventually.
You usually spend a lot,
and you're particular about your clothes.
This welcoming gift
can help solve some practical problems.
Your salary will continue to be paid.
Four thousand US dollars a month,
just as a part-time consultant.
It's very simple.
If I reject your bribes,
how will you coerce me?
The stakes are high.
Of course, you need to think it over.
No rush to answer.
This passport
was recovered by the police.
Since you called the police via the hotel,
the thief happened to be caught.
As for your colleague,
he was completely unaware when
he allegedly brought a minor to the hotel.
Call the police.
Maricotre Hotel.
Someone's trying to rape an underage girl.
We need you here immediately.
Liaoping, I'm innocent!
He will also
be freed once his innocence is verified.
But this incident will remain on record,
and become the focus of the delegation.
Therefore, our conversation
won't be known by a third person.
Either
you return home normally,
and we'll pretend we never met.
Or
you stay and wait for a new passport,
and we continue our deep conversation.
Mr. Cao, let's go.
Okay.
Comrade Zhu Yingjia
will replace Jiang Zaizhen
as Deputy Director of the 4th Department,
taking sole charge of
"enemy-line" dispatch and intel gathering.
I hope you will remain steadfastly loyal
and serve the Party and State.
Sending our core personnel to the mainland
has now become normalized.
In the near term,
we will further increase pace and numbers.
As for the results,
they remain inconsistent.
Regarding recent developments,
we are all well aware of the situation.
Deputy Director Zhu here
has spent years fighting the enemy,
and has extensive practical experience.
He has prepared a sweeping reform plan.
Deputy Director Zhu,
please go ahead.
Jiang Zaizhen's defection
isn't entirely a bad thing.
It's also an opportunity.
Why not analyze her motives deeply?
Why not use this to drive forward
legislation and reform?
To give an example,
if any of our compatriots,
regardless of their status,
even myself included,
even if mainland State Security
suspects or arrests them,
detains, questions, or even turns them,
if they return and are willing to talk,
even if they are our government officials
or our own agents sent to the mainland,
as long as they tell the whole truth,
all past actions will be forgiven,
and their pensions guaranteed,
so that no one has any lingering worries.
Only a system like this
can motivate more young people
to willingly risk their lives.
Hello.
I'm here to report for duty.
What time were you told to be here?
Before eight.
It's only 7:40.
I'm not late.
Just wait.
I already rang the bell.
By the way,
my last name is Gong.
Gong as in "palace."
You can just call me Xiao Gong.
There are rules here.
No names allowed.
Didn't you know?
You're here to report for duty, right?
First of all, welcome, everyone.
You've all been carefully selected.
Now, please introduce yourselves.
You there, you go first.
Li Huadong.
Born in Guangdong in 1972.
Height: 180 centimeters.
Stop, stop, stop.
Why don't you add your weight, blood type,
home address, and your resume,
attach a photo,
and publish it in the newspaper?
Weren't we to introduce ourselves?
Not even in class.
Haven't you ever watched a spy movie?
East and West Germany, the two Koreas,
the US and the Soviet Union.
Which of them didn't have spies
in each other's ranks?
How can you be sure that among us here,
there are no enemy moles?
Maybe he is one.
Him, or him.
Lesson one, section one, point one:
Whatever people ask you,
don't answer if it's not necessary.
Continue.
You can all call me Xiao Li.
I'm 22, a police academy graduate.
I've interned in the public security system.
With excellent grades.
My Party membership date
is probably the earliest among my peers.
Sit down.
You go next.
Yes, you.
You can all call me Xiao Wu.
Wu, the word 'five' with a person radical.
Though I ranked first in the city's exam,
I feel I still have room for improvement.
I hope to learn a lot from everyone.
Within that humility
lies a hint of
pride.
Sit down.
Reporting!
Didn't Comrade Li Fengge inform you
that you can't be late for class?
I'm not late.
It's not even 8:00 yet.
You stand and listen.
There's no seat for you.
Close the door.
Let me go over the rules.
First, do not be late.
Second,
until the training is over,
none of you
are allowed to ask each other about
your identities and backgrounds.
Third, according to our superiors' orders,
the teaching method this time will be reformed.
You are all part of a pilot program.
Did I tell you to move?
I'd distract others standing on the side.
They won't see me if I stand in the back.
During the training period,
the bureau will randomly come pick people.
Half your time will be out on missions,
and half your time in class.
Apply what you learn.
I hope you'll adjust your attitudes.
You must know that this
isn't the classroom where you slacked off.
This is a classified unit,
a disciplined force.
Is that clear?
Clear!
Director.
See for yourself.
That fast?
Not fast enough.
Then...
Come help me with these eye drops.
The rookies lack experience.
Sending them over now...
...means a high chance of failure.
They'd likely be going to their deaths.
There's no time, Old Zhu.
Here.
And this side.
If this Lee...
...ever sets foot on US soil...
...you know the cross-strait dynamic...
...will turn into.
If I were him...
...either I wouldn't go...
...or if I did...
...those extreme remarks...
...I'd definitely make them.
Without making those extreme remarks...
...what's the point of going?
Right?
But once he does...
...what will the CCP think?
What moves will they make?
Have you thought about it?
Drills.
Live-fire drills.
Or even an accidental discharge...
...sparking a war.
Those tasks you're handling...
...need to be sped up too.
Missile intel, military maps...
Even the tiniest scraps...
...I won't turn down.
Taiwan, China...
...must make preparations early.
Understood.
Old Zhu...
...don't you have a lot of seeds?
Scatter them all across the mainland.
Don't hold a single one back.
If they aren't planted in the dirt...
...how will you know which will die...
...and which will survive?
Attention, all passengers.
You have entered the inspection area.
Please have your ID cards,
passports, and related documents ready
for customs security checks.
Do not carry contraband or banned books.
For inquiries, visit the information desk.
Hold on.
Where are you headed?
Kyrgyzstan.
What was that?
A-Zheng.
Come here. Come with me.
Please cooperate with the inspection.
You in the glasses.
Yes, you.
Is there a problem?
We'll find out once we check, won't we?
Where are you headed?
Here's my ticket.
You can see for yourself.
I'm asking you, so answer me.
Understand?
Xiamen.
ID card.
Where did you get this?
Where's the old one?
Everyone is required to get a new ID.
Aren't you replacing yours?
Bring the box over.
Bring the box over for inspection.
Put it here?
Open the box.
Be careful, will you?
Don't move.
I'm checking.
Step back.
Search.
What's this?
A book.
What kind of book?
An ancient book.
Of course I know it's ancient.
It's a banned book.
Don't you know?
Mao Shi Zheng Yi.
A research work on the Classic of Poetry.
Also known as Kong Shu.
In the 16th year of the Zhenguan reign,
written by Kong Yingda by imperial decree.
One of the Wu Jing Zheng Yi.
It was an officially issued book back then.
All right, all right.
Page seven, line four.
What does it say? Read it out.
I thought you knew it all.
Sounding so smart.
Can't remember it now?
Smuggling contraband.
Seized for inspection. Confiscated.
You can go.
Keep your new ID card safe.
What are you shaking your head for?
Want us to search you again?
We have a room over there.
I don't want the book anymore.
That's what I thought.
Stop pretending to be an intellectual.
What are you doing? Studying?
The higher-ups want you to go back.
Before the end of your shift.
Don't be late.
Go back for what?
To give you a bonus.
What do you think?
Said they're handing out new houses and cars.
And a girl for you, too.
Can't even get peace after work.
I have to monitor Liu Dengshi later.
What the hell happened now?
What else?
Getting new IDs and taking photos.
Getting a new lease on life.
I don't quite get it.
What exactly is Lee Teng-hui up to?
Removing ancestral homes,
replacing them with birthplaces.
From Ronghai/Zhangzhou to Taipei/Kaohsiung.
Will everyone vote for him then?
You.
Just call the higher-ups directly
and ask them.
Over a decade ago,
in the mainland,
those catching Taiwan, China broadcasts
would occasionally hear
Taiwan, China's codes for sleeper agents.
These coded messages
usually
used four-character codes for orders.
Taiwan, China agents in the mainland
will continue to receive such codes.
So listen up, everyone.
Some of you, or perhaps one of you,
might spend decades of your lives
trying to crack them.
Comrade 39533, please record.
225.
5963.
Numbers are the keyhole.
The codebook is the key.
Only unlocking the message word by word
can it surface.
Who are you?
Branches from the plant blocked the way.
I moved it.
You didn't notice.
If you placed it there on purpose,
to see if anyone had entered the room,
then today was pointless.
I left a very obvious mark
on your door lock,
and you didn't notice that either.
That is just terrible.
Who exactly are you?
Military Intelligence, 4th Department.
The new Deputy Director.
Your direct superior.
Sir.
I've read your file.
Your overall grades are average.
Your military skills are also average.
But you're quite good with numbers.
You know how to do business.
You ran a clothing factory with your dad.
You're smart.
You even ran a small business in the army.
Why do you want to work in intelligence?
Reporting, sir.
To fight to defend Taiwan, China.
I was born in Taipei,
and when I die, I'll be buried in Taipei.
I enlisted
for the sake of future peace.
Out of loyalty and conviction.
Try again.
I can see right through those lies.
What is your current assignment?
On odd days, I inspect customs packages.
On even days,
I keep an eye on Liu Dengshi.
When greed goes too far,
it's called corruption.
When arrogance goes too far,
it's called tyranny.
That is our government's current state.
Those in power are a tumor, a cancer.
You watch me during the day,
and you watch me at night.
Why don't you just arrest me?
It'd save us all the trouble.
He's that...
professor always bashing the government.
Doing such a boring job
for two whole years...
Of course I'd be unhappy.
If you had a choice,
what would you want to do?
Sir,
many people from my class...
Some went to Japan,
some went to Europe to study abroad.
And some others
went to the mainland.
High budgets, fast promotions.
I hear they're living it up every day.
I'm the only one stuck here.
I want to get out there, too.
Take a walk with me.
Answer me.
What does "centrally dispatched" mean?
Agents sent to the mainland.
Why use official personnel?
Enlist first, then train.
Higher caliber and clearer minds.
They know what the priorities are.
They know what to do.
Once these people reach the mainland,
the intel they gather isn't written down.
They won't leave any evidence.
Everything is kept in their heads.
No secret code needed for Taiwan, China.
Once these people return,
they can compile the intel they gathered.
It's secure communication.
Look at Taipei down below.
It's not as peaceful as it looks.
Many CPC agents are right beside us.
Think about it.
Forty or fifty years ago,
even Chiang had Communists by his side.
How do you know how many are left now?
Enemies are among us,
and we are among them.
That's how intelligence work goes.
Our opponent has planted eyes around us,
and we have multiple ears on their side.
Your ancestral home is Ronghai.
Your grandfather speaks Zhangzhou dialect.
You have a living great-aunt there.
You possess many favorable qualifications.
Comrade Lin Kanshan,
to penetrate deep behind "enemy lines",
you will depart soon.
Pose as a businessman from Taiwan, China.
Your codename is North Wind.
Yes, sir.
Buy rice today,
deliver flour tomorrow.
I'll send you messages via radio.
Do exactly as I say.
Don't ask about what I haven't mentioned.
Sometimes, the less you know,
the safer you are.
Perhaps,
before long,
Lee Teng-hui will "visit the US".
Just watch.
The Taiwan Strait won't be peaceful.
Therefore,
you must watch all mainland movements,
from the military to the missiles.
There might even be live-fire exercises.
This is the most critical part.
So the more intel you get,
the lower the chances of war.
The mainland has, in Taiwan, China,
also planted and trained many people.
Don't think they aren't watching you.
Have a good drink today.
When you wake up tomorrow,
distance yourself from all your friends,
and make everyone forget you.
Hurry up and
put on a new face.
Go gamble.
Go lose.
Borrow all the money you can.
Burden yourself with unpayable debts.
Go get into fights.
Go be a deadbeat.
Make everyone avoid you,
to dispel all suspicions.
You need to turn yourself
into a desperate loser.
The more thorough of a loser you are,
the safer you'll be on the mainland.
Don't run!
Freeze!
You're all skilled professionals.
Ensure that even if you're fired,
you can still find a new job out there.
Continue.
When training to be a tour guide,
you must actually go and get
your tour guide certificate.
Not only must you be familiar with
all the attractions in Minzhong,
but also those in surrounding cities.
Like Mount Wuyi,
Gulangyu Island,
Yongding Tulou,
and the Mazu Temple.
No matter where you go,
you must be able to talk endlessly.
Understood?
Understood!
Don't be shy. Come on.
You are a seed.
Planted there, you must survive first.
Strive to grow into the tallest one.
I'm surely not the only seed.
Have any withered away?
Crossing the street is risky too.
You can catch a virus just breathing.
If you're that afraid,
you might as well just stay home.
I'm not afraid.
Gathering intelligence,
acting as a courier,
I can do it all.
These gentlemen here
are all big bosses.
They all do business with the mainland.
They're all your seniors.
This young friend of mine
also wants to open a factory on the mainland.
His family is in the textile business.
He's a young man with ambition.
He wants to make money, of course.
He wants to make his mark in the world.
The mainland is reforming and opening up.
Communist money is still money.
I invited you all here
to teach him
how to do business with mainlanders.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Thank you, bosses.
Thank you, seniors.
I look forward to your guidance.
Come on.
Finish this drink.
This...
Zhu, why bother?
You're a long-term asset.
Find a way to scout
and recruit anyone we can use.
From the government, the military,
the corporate, financial, or tech sectors.
The more, the better.
A toast to you, brothers.
Good, good, good.
Lao Zhu.
I'm definitely taking you under my wing.
Please look out for me, Brother Bin.
Come, come.
You're not just doing this for yourself.
Besides your future and mine,
there's also the future of Taiwan, China.
It's all resting in your hands now.
I'm willing to go.
Even if it means death.
Don't die.
Stay alive.
Remember,
under no circumstances
should you do anything "at all costs."
Go there safe and sound,
and come back safe and sound.
Starting today, everyone,
you need to come up with an alias.
Pair up in twos.
Train in your groups.
Keep each other alert.
What should this alias be?
It should be based on your
real experiences,
mixed with some fabricated ones.
Blend truth and lies together.
From now on, at work
and life, use each other's aliases.
Think about it based on your situation.
I want to partner with you.
Are you willing?
I thought you'd pick someone else.
Although you're a bit slow to react,
you're very detail-oriented.
I think I'm pretty steady,
but my mom says I'm impatient.
We can complement each other.
Let me add one more thing.
About the pairings,
they must follow your trainee ID numbers.
One with Two, Three with Four,
Five with Six, and so on.
Comrades who have decided on an alias
can go find your partners.
I'm 1973-
02240013.
How about you?
I'm Number Five.
You're Number Thirteen.
Hello, Number Five.
I'm Number Six, Huadong.
Hello.
Jinlan.
My name is He Chunxiao.
I am Wang Kai.
Inviting you to watch the TV drama
"Crossfire"
From your first minute in this business,
you should have known this day would come.
Who told you to do this?
This is against the rules.
Here is a piece of Class-A intelligence.
MIB wants me to activate someone.
Name, identity?
He's left-handed and takes photos.
Cover identity?
Probably a photographer.
What are you here to do?
It's International Investment Month.
Making some investments.
New trainees assigned to each division.
The usual rules.
Guide and mentor them.
They're all promising recruits.